

# Game Producer / Project Manager





acjh13@gmail.com



Highly adaptive and multi-disciplinary Producer / Project Manager. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

# Experience

**Production Intern** | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - *Final Fantasy Brave Exvius* Sept 2020 – Present

- Prepared and maintained monthly and weekly event lists for content updates with <u>Google Sheets</u> and <u>Confluence</u>
- Created and followed-up on Design team tasks with <u>Jira</u> after <u>Daily Scrum</u>
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating new ticketing workflow
- Took initiative to create scripts to streamline production workflow

# **Production Teaching Assistant** | DigiPen Singapore Sept 2019 – Mar 2020

- Advised student game teams on project scoping and task scheduling
- Mediated cross-discipline discussions and conflicts
- Assisted teams with resolving project scope and scheduling issues

## **Projects**

### **Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer**

Kindred | Sept 2019 - June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D single player narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Communicated game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted <u>Agile</u> methodology with weekly <u>Scrum</u> meetings and <u>Kanban</u> task boards
- Created <u>cross-department workflows</u> for better communication
- Finalist in multiple categories, DigiPen Game Awards 2020

### **Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer**

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Organized weekly meetings with team members
- Worked with lecturers and team members to overcome internal conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

For more details on my projects, see my Portfolio!

## Education

# BSc Computer Science and Game Design

DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore Sept 2017 – May 2021 (Expected)

• Dean's Honour List, Fall 2019

# Skills

#### **Soft Skills**

- Effective Communication
- Problem Solving
- Organisation

### **Management Methods**

- Agile
- Scrum
- Kanban

# **Management Software**

- Jira
- Confluence
- Trello
- Microsoft Excel
- Google Sheets
- HacknPlan

### **Software & Tools**

- Git / SVN
- Microsoft Office
- Visual Studio
- Unity
- Unreal Engine 4
- Custom Game Engine(s)

### **Programming & Scripting**

- C/C++
- C#
- Python
- JavaScript